We can't even go a week without this one.
While rallying his supporters, Donald Trump casted his vision for 2024 and beyond.
Let's just take a gander.
We're going to rebuild our cities.
We're going to bring them back like they used to be.
We're going to make them safe places again.
We're going to give our police their power back and we're going to give them immunity
from prosecution so they're not prosecuted for doing their job.
So I just want to address something because sometimes when he's talking, I think that
people get so caught up in just how wild he sounds that they don't realize what he's actually
saying.
So he said the police are going to get their power back.
They're no longer going to be prosecuted for doing their job.
He also said we're going to take our cities back.
So this is somebody who is blatantly saying he thinks it's the police's job to kill unarmed
citizens because that's what they get prosecuted for.
When he says we're going to take back our cities, he is saying we are going to redline.
We are going to arrest at will.
We are going to segregate our cities.
Well, the scary part about it is that when you look at Joe Biden, he's doing an old other
version of wackness.
It's just the same.
You know, so I say all of that to say we praying for a miracle at this point.
We are, we are, we are.